Guide to the Andrews Memorial Bookplate Collection of Irene D. Andrews Pace (School and College Bookplates)
Yale University Arts Library
Andrews Memorial Bookplate Collection of Irene D. Andrews Pace (School and College Bookplates)
1700-1960
1900-1960
BKP 4
Yale University Arts Library
2.09
(5 boxes)
The collection contains examples of bookplates from various academic institutions. The collection also contains correspondence, related factual information cut out from catalogs or journals, and some handwritten notes by the collector.
2.5 linear feet (5 boxes)
Andrews, Irene Dwen, 1892-
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Irene D. Andrews Pace, 1963, in memory of Dr. Edmund Andrews (Yale 1913) and his father, Dr. E. Wyllys Andrews.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Biographical / Historical
Born Irene Greene Dwen, Mrs. Pace (1892-1962) was an avid bookplate collector from the early 1920s until 1962. In addition to over 150,000 plates in her collection, she also maintained a reference library related to bookplates as well as heraldry and biographical research. Pace commissioned several hundred bookplates for herself. In 1936, she published Owners of Books: The Dissipations of a Collector.
Scope and Contents
The collection contains examples of bookplates from various academic institutions. In addition to bookplates, the collection also contains correspondence, related factual information cut out from catalogs or journals, and some handwritten notes by the collector.
Arrangement
Arranged alphabetically by the name of the institution. Institutions with the names of the saints were grouped together and ordered alphabetically under the name of Saint. Abbreviations such as San, St., S, etc. were ignored. Any unidentified schools are grouped together at the end.
Any correspondence or ephemeral materials relating to a specific bookplate are filed together with the bookplate. If known, the artist and date of the bookplate have been recorded as well as the location of the school. Multiple copies of bookplates are also noted.
Bookplates -- Specimens.; Bookplates; Andrews, Irene Dwen, 1892-
- Bookplates
  - A – C (Box 1, Folder 1-7)
    - Abbatiae B. Mariae Virg. A Monte-Serrano, Brazil, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Abbatiae S. Gregori Magni de Downside, Rome, Italy, 1900 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      Scope and Contents
      G. Ferloni, artist
    - Abbatis Sanctae Fidei Conques, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      H. Herry, artist
    - Aberdeen Grammar School, Scotland, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Academia Augusta, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Academia Figueirense, Portugal, undated; 4 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Academia Jose Antonio, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      R. Abad, artist
    - Academia Library, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Academia Valenciana de Letras, Brazil, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Academiae Bellas Artes Sabadell, Spain, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Academie de la Rochelle, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Academiska Foreningens, Lund, Sweden, undated; 2 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Academy of the Sacred Heart, San Francisco, CA, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
      Dorothy Payne, artist
    - Acad. Reg. IIIB. Inst., 1786 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Adams School Library, 1921 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      Winifred V. Collins, artist
    - Adelphi College Library, Garden City, NY, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Adrian College, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Agnes Scott College, Decatur, GA, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
      [S. B. P.], artist
    - Agriculture and Mechanic Arts College of New Hampshire, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Alabama Polytechnic Institute Library, undated; 2 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Albion College, Michigan, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Alderny Public School, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Alma College Library, Michigan, undated; 11 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Alston College, Lancashire, UK, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - American Academy of Arts and Sciences, 1790 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - American Institute, Upsala University, Sweden, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - American School of Classical Studies at Athens, Greece, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Amherst College, Massachusetts, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
      F. Schuyler Mathews, artist
    - Amherst College Library, Massachusetts, undated; 4 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Amherst College Athenae Library, Massachusetts, undated; 3 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Anna Sandströms Skola, Uppsala, Sweden, 1903 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      Ingegerd Mannerstråle, artist
    - Annesly Hall, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Antioch College, Yellow Spring, OH, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Apud Scholam, undated; 2 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Arbetare Institutets Bibliotek of Stockholm, Sweden, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Art Institute of Chicago, The, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Ashbourne Grammar School, Queen Elizabeth I. Grammar School, Derbyshire, England, UK, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Ashburton Grammar School, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Auburn Theological School, New York, NY, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Auburn Theological Seminary, undated; 4 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Aug. College, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Aulae B. M. V. Oxon, Oxford University Library, undated; 3 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Baker University, undated; 6 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Ball. Coll. Oxon. Soc., Balliol College, Oxford Society, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Bangor Theological Seminary, Maine, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Barvicensis Academy, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Bath Literary Institution, Bath Royal Literary and Scientific Institution, UK, 1824 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Baylor University, Waco, TX, undated; 2 bookplates, 1 envelope (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Beaumont College, Old Windsor, UK, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Bedford College, undated; 4 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      E. Barclay, artist
    - Bedford College Library, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Bedford House Academy, Brixton, circa 1790 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Bentley School of Accounting and Finance, Waltham, MA, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
      C. A. Capon, artist
    - Accademia Carrara di Belle Arti di Bergamo, Italy, 1930 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      Z. di L. Angelini, artist
    - Berkeley College, Berlin, Germany, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Berwick Academy, South Berwick, ME, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Bibl. C. S. Franc. Cort, Turin, Italy, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Biblioteca Central Universidade do Brasil, Rio de Janeiro, Brazil, 1954; 2 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      Alberto Lima, artist
    - Biblioteca da Faculdade de Direito de Sao Paola, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Biblioteca Dell'Istituto Guiridico, Turin, Italy, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Biblioteca Dell Seminario Arcivescoville, Turin, Italy, undated; 7 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Biblioteca Seminario, Turin, Italy, undated; 4 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Biblioteca Universaria Di Bologna, Italy, 1917; 2 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      A. Majani, artist
    - Biblioteka Uniwersytecka W Lodzi, Poland, 1960; 1; bookplate (Box 1, Folder 2)
      J. Tusinski, artist
    - Biblioteka Uniwersytecka W Wilnie, Poland, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
      I. H., artist
    - Biblioth. Conv. San Torino, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Bibl. Nazionale, Universitaria Torino, Italy, undated; 4 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Bibliotheca Seminarii Willibaldini Eystadii, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Bibliotheque Americaine de L'universite Strasbourg, France, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Bishopsgate Institute, City University, London, England, UK, 1903; 3 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      G. H. McCall, artist
    - Bishopsgate Institute, City University, London, England, UK, 1894; 2 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      Walter Crane, artist
    - Blackheath Proprietary School, Blackheath, London, England, UK, undated; 2 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Bloomfield Hills School, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
      M. Curtis Stanford, artist
    - Blue Coat School, Westminster, England, UK, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Blundells School Tiverton, Devon, England, UK, 1790; 3 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      T. Foot, artist
    - Boston College, Chestnut Hill, MA, undated; 2 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Bibliotheca Collegii Regalis Aberdonensis, Aberdeen, Scotland, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Boston Girls' High and Normal School, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Boston University, undated; 6 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Botanical Institute, Debrecen University, Hungary, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      K. Varkonyi, artist
    - Bowdoin College, Brunswick, ME, undated; 13 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Bowdoin College, undated; 2 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      William Edgar Fisher, artist
    - Bowdoin College Library, undated; 2 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      John A. Lowell & Co., artist
    - Boyce Thompson Institute for Plant Research, Yonkers, NY, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Brown University, Providence, RI, undated; 30 items, 1 copper engraving (Box 1, Folder 3)
      T. Johnson, artist
    - Brünn Technical School (now Vysoka Skola Technicka v Brne), Czech Republic, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Brunensis University, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Bryn Mawr College Library, Pennsylvania, undated; 2 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Buckeburg Institute of Music, Germany, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
      O. H., artist
    - Buffalo State Normal School, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Boys' High School, Atlanta, GA, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      H. M. S., artist
    - Bramham College, Leeds, Yorkshire, England, UK, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
      J. Y. Knight & Co., artist
    - Brasenose College, Oxford University, UK, undated; 2 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Brearley School Library, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Brighton College, undated; 2 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Bromsgrove School Library, UK, undated; 2 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      T. K. M., del.; P. H. D., sc.
    - Brooklyn Female Academy, Packer Collegiate Institute, Brooklyn, NY, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - California College Library, Vacaville, CA, undated; 2 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - California Preparatory School for Boys, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Cambridge High School, Cambridge, UK, undated; 3 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Cambridge Academy, University of Cambridge, UK, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Cambridge University, undated; 2 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Capituli Primatialis Ecclesiae Pisanae, Italy, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Capitulum Eccl. Cath.Tarvisinae-Treviso, Italy, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Carm. Disc. Conv. Lugd, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Casale Monserrato Seminario, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Case School of Applied Science, Cleveland, OH, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Catalan Institute of the Arts of the Book, Barcelona, Catalonia, Spain, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Catholic University Peking, undated; 2 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Catholic University, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - C. Cumber's School Library [Hahira, GA?], undated; 3 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      Fothergill, artist
    - Central High School Library, Columbus, OH, undated; 1 bookplate, 1 envelope (Box 1, Folder 4)
      Lam Woo, artist
    - Central High School Library, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
      Clarence Gallogly, artist
    - Channing House School, Highgate, London, England, UK, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Charlestown Female Seminary (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Convent of Burdigal, undated; 4 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Charter House, undated; 2 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Charter House School, London, England, UK, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Cheltenham College, Gloucestershire, England, UK, 1841 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Librarium Collegii Cheltoniensis, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Cheshunt College, undated; 9 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      S. T., artist
    - Chieri Seminario Arcivescovile, Turin, Italy, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Cholmley School Library, Highgate, London, England, UK, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Christo School Library, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
      Ella Dwyer, artist
    - Christ's College, Cambridge, University of Cambridge, UK, undated; 2 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Christ College Cantab, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Christ's College, Oxford, University of Oxford, UK, undated; 9 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Cincinnati Law School Library, University of Cincinnati, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Cittadella Boarding School, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - City of London School, London, England, UK, undated; 8 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Clare College, Cambridge, University of Cambridge, UK, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Claremont Men's College (now Claremont McKenna College), undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Clarendon College, Oxford, University of Oxford, UK, 1893 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      T. G. J., artist
    - Clark University, Worcester, MA, undated; 21 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Clark University, Worcester, MA (Box 1, Folder 5)
      Mabel C. Gage, del.; E. D. French, sc.
    - Class of 1914, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
      S. Otis, arist
    - Clemson College, Clemson University, South Carolina, undated; 2 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Cleveland School of Art, undated; 2 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Clifton College, Bristol, England, UK, undated; 2 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Cloyne House Library, Cloyne, County Cork, Ireland, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Coll. Camberiacensis Societ. Jesu, Turin, Italy, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Coll. Christi Regis S. J. Torontonense, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      Leslie Victor Smith, artist
    - Coll. Di S. Maurizio Torre Pellice, Turin, Italy, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - College of New Jersey, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - College Nobil.B.V.de Carm. Taurin Societ Jesu Torino, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - College of Preachers, Boston, MA, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
      Alanson C. Sturgis, artist
    - College of Physicians and Surgeons, Quine Library, University of Illinois at Urbana, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - College of Preceptors, UK, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - College of Puget Sound Library, University of Puget Sound, WA, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - College of Saint. Teresa, Winona, MN, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - College of Saint. Thomas, Minnesota, undated; 3 bookplates, 1 note, 1 publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
      Swann, artist
    - College of Saints Peter and Paul, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - College of the City of New York, undated; 4 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - College of William and Mary, Virginia, undated; 9 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - College Ste. Barbe, Gand, Ghent, Belgium, undated; 2 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Collegiate & Commercial Academy, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Collegiate School, Garnet Hill, Glasgow, Scotland, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - College Taur. Soc. Jes. Cat. Insc. Excensu Reg. Cel. Vic Ami-Torino, Italy, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Colleges, Turin, Italy, undated; 4 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Collegii Alberti Magni in Novo Porto, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Collegii Capellani, Oxford, England, UK, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Collegii Joannis Baptistae, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Collegii Londinensis, UK, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Collegii Sanctae Crucis, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
      border by Isaiah Thomas
    - Collegii Sancti Caroli, London, England, UK, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Collegii Sancti Cuthberti, UK, undated; 2 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Collegio Artigianelli Torino, Italy, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Collegio Degli Avvocati Torino, Italy, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Collegio de Ntra. Sra. De Regla, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Collegio del S. Rosario, Venice, Italy, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Collegio Official de Medicos, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Collegio Sancti Davidis, 1844 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Collegio S. Bernardi, 1724 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Collegium Armorum, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Collegium Iowense, undated; 2 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Collegium Stae. Mariae Immaculatae apud Woolhampton, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Collegium Cluenense Soc. Jesu, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Collingwood High School, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Coll. Reg. S. J. AD S. Georg, Torino, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Coll. S. Benecti, Fort Augustus, Scotland, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Coll. S. Georgii Magni, Downside, UK, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Columbia College Library, Columbia University, New York, NY, undated; 2 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      Alex Anderson, artist
    - Columbia College, Columbia University, New York, NY, undated; 10 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Columbia University, New York, NY, undated; 56; bookplate (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Columbia University, New York, NY, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
      Cosmos and Nashburn, artist
    - Columbia University, New York, NY, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
      G. Viafora, artist
    - Columbia University, New York, NY, undated; 1; bookplate (Box 1, Folder 6)
      S. Alabaster, artist
    - Columbus School for Girls, Columbus, OH, undated; 3 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Commercial High School, undated; 2 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      Hogeboom, artist
    - Connecticut College for Women (now Connecticut College), New London, CT, undated; 1; bookplate (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Conventes. S. Francisci Trini, Turin, Italy, 1707 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      Fr. Michaelangus, sc.
    - Conventus Monacensis, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Convitto Ecclesiastico, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Conv. S. Mariae de Spineta, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
      Diego Donati, artist
    - Cornell University, Ithaca, NY, undated; 4 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Cornell University, Ithaca, NY, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
      Katherine Fuertes, artist
    - Corpus Christi College, Cambridge, University of Cambridge, UK, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
      Batchelor, artist
    - Corpus Christi College, Cambridge, University of Cambridge, UK, undated; 4 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Cranleigh School, Cranleigh, Surrey, UK, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Crow Hall Academy, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Crozer Theological Seminary, undated; 2 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Cuzco National University Library, Cuzco, Peru, undated; 1; bookplate (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Cuneo Conv. S. Marie Angelorum (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - D – K (Box 2, Folder 8-17)
    - Dame Alice Owen's Girls' School, Potter's Bar, UK, undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Dartmouth College, Hanover, NH, undated; 17 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Dartmouth College, Hanover, NH, undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
      F. G. Moone, artist
    - Dartmouth College Library, Hanover, NH, undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
      Mahonri Young, artist
    - Dartmouth College Library, Hanover, NH, undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
      JWS, artist
    - Dartmouth College, Hanover, NH, undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
      artists: Homer Eaton Keyes, Charles R. Capon, Adam Pietz
    - Dauntsey's School, West Lavington, Wiltshire, UK, undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
      Reginall Hazell, artist
    - Denison University, Granville, OH, undated; 4 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Denton Industrial College, Denton, TX, undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Des Moines College, undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Devonport Classical and Mathematical School, Devonport, Devon, UK, undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - De Witt Clinton High School, Bronx, NY, undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Dolgarrog Institute, Wells, UK, undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Dominican College Library, New Orleans, LA, undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Dominican Convent, Verona, Italy, undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Downside Abbey, Stratton-on-the-Fosse, Somerset, UK, 1907 (Box 2, Folder 8)
      M. L. C., artist
    - Downside College, Stratton-on-the-Fosse, Somerset, UK, 1907; 8 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Downside School, Bath, UK, undated; 3 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Drexel Institute (now Drexel University), Philadelphia, PA, undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Drury College Library, undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Duisburg Schule, Germany, undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
      Erich Makowski, artist
    - Dulwich College, London, UK, undated; 4 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Dulwich College Preparatory School, London, UK, undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Dummer Academy (now the Governor's Academy; was also formerly Governor Dummer Academy), Byfield, MA, undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Durham University, Durham, UK, undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Dunelm Univ. Coll., undated; 5 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Eastbourne College Cavendish Library, Eastbourne, England, UK, undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - East High School, undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
      Dreka.Phila (Louis Dreka of Philadelphia), artist
    - East India College (the training organization for the British East India Company), Hertfordshire, UK, undated; 5 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - East London University Settlement, London, UK, undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Earlham College, Richmond, IN, undated; 2 (Box 2, Folder 9)
      Howard Lee, artist
    - Ecclesiae Lochemensis, undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Ecclesiae Sancti Nicolai, Storkyrkoförsamlingen, Stockholm, Sweden, 1934 (Box 2, Folder 9)
      Brita Grep, artist
    - Ecole Normale Emile Andre, Bruxelles, Belgium, undated; 2 (Box 2, Folder 9)
      Mrs. Callet-Carcado, artist
    - Edgeworth School, undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Edward VI Grammar School, Norwich, UK, undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Electrical Standardizing Testing and Training Institution, 1891 (Box 2, Folder 9)
      T. S. Harrison, artist
    - Elmira College, Elmira, NY, undated; 10; bookplate (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Ely Theological College, Ely, Cambs, UK, undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Collegii Theologici Eliensis, undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Elyria High School, undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - English Grammar School, Dublin, Ireland, circa 1760 (Box 2, Folder 9)
      W. Esdall, artist
    - Enniskillen School, Enniskillen, UK, undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Emmanuel College Cambridge, UK, undated; 4 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Emmanuel College Cambridge, UK, 1737 (Box 2, Folder 9)
      W. Stephens, artist
    - Episcopal Theological School, Cambridge, MA, undated; 3 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Epsom College, Surrey, KT, UK, undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Erasmus Hall High School, New York, undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Erzsebet School, undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Escola Secundaria Santa Maria Do Olival, Escola Industrial e Comercial, Tomar, Portugal, undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Escola Profissional De Paia, Portugal, undated; 2 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Escuela De Aplicacion Y Tiro De Artilleria, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Escuela De Estado Mayor, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Escuela De Ingenieros, Universitat Polytetecnica (Valencia, Spain), 1946 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Escuela Municipal De Artes Y Oficios De Reus, 1911 (Box 2, Folder 9)
      R. Casals y Vernis, artist
    - Essex Institute, undated; 2 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Eton College, Windsor, England, UK, undated; 15 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Eureka College, Eureka, IL, undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Evansville College, Evansville, IN, undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Exeter College Oxford, England, UK, undated; 2 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Exeter High School, Exeter, England, UK, undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Faculdade Fluminense De Filosofia, Brazil, undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Falconer High School, New York, undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Farrington Ward School, undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Fauconberge School, Suffolk, England, UK, undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Firth College (now Sheffield University), UK, undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
      F. D. New, artist; Parkin and Bacon, sc.
    - Fisk University, Nashville, TN, undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Flora Stone Mather College, Cleveland, OH, undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Franklin & Marshall College, Lancaster, PA, undated; 5 (Box 2, Folder 10)
      Mrs. John B. Kieffer, artist
    - Fraser Institute, undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Frome School of Arts and Science, undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Funck Professional School, undated (Box 2, Folder 10)